Are you ready for an advanced combo with you rocking reverse undulation? I'm Johanna, and this is Karen, and we're here with Hip Expressions Belly Dance Studio in St. Petersburg, Florida.
So let's start with our rocking reverse undulation traveling backwards. So our right foot's going to be back, our timing is scooping in the back.
Ready, and, back, two, three, roll up.
Keep it going, and back, two, three, roll up.
Good.
Now we're going to switch it to going forward.
Slow it down.
Six, seven, eight.
Now forward, back, forward, back, forward, back, forward, back.
Now we're going to switch it going back.
Forward, six, seven, eight.
And back, front, back.
And I'll do it from the side so you can see.
Switch it forward just a little faster.
And it's forward, back, forward, forward, back and hold.
And back, forward, back, back and hold, and forward two, three, four, forward two, three and switch.
Back two, three, back two, three.
Good.
Make sure you practice that in front of a mirror, and soon you'll have a nice, smooth undulation that goes forward and back.